

Profile

Software Developer with emphasis in Web Applications. Experience in the implementation of educational services, virtual platforms, and project coordination. High interest in developing personal and professional capacities with strengths such as teamwork, innovation, and responsibility. Experience with tools such as Python, Javascript, HTML, CSS, React, Flask, Node.js, Express and use of relational and non relational databases such as MySQL and MongoDB.

Employment History

IT Coordinator at British International School, Barranquilla August 2018 — Present

Coordination of educational platforms and development of workshops for the school community. Implementation and management of training and workshops for teachers and students in the use of technology/virtual platforms Coordination of academic events for the institution.

Assistant Teacher at British International School, Barranquilla August 2016 — June 2018

Monitoring of students with special needs within the 3rd grade of Primary. Constant collaboration with teachers from different areas. Dictation of classes such as English, Mathematics, Spanish and Science.

Assistant Psychologist at British International School, Barranquilla February 2015 — June 2016

Admissions processes, academic and psychological monitoring of students with special needs, and creation of guides for parents and teachers on behavior management. Development of behavior improvement workshops for students.

Psychology Internship at British International School, Barranquilla February 2015 — June 2015

Collaboration across each of the school's sections with mental and behavioral follow up of the students. Workshop and project development for the school.

Details

Cra. 55 # 75 - 119
Barranquilla, 08001
Colombia
+573017823403
magv181091@gmail.com
LinkedIn
GitHub Repository

Date / Place of birth October 18th, 1991 Barranquilla

Nationality Colombian

Skills

Computer Skills

Fast Learner

Customer Service

Highly organized and efficient

Languages

Spanish

English

Hobbies

Boxing, Guitar, Video editing, Web Development.

Education

Skills in Programming with emphasis in Web, Universidad del Norte, Barranquilla

April 2021 - December 2021

Psychologist, Universidad del Norte, Barranquilla

July 2010 — September 2015

High School Diploma, Colegio Real - Royal School, Barranquilla

August 2004 - June 2010

Courses

Web Applications Development, Universidad del Norte, Barranquilla

October 2021 — December 2021

Software Development, Universidad del Norte, Barranquilla

August 2021 — October 2021

Basic Programming, Universidad del Norte, Barranquilla

June 2021 — August 2021

Programming Fundamentals, Universidad del Norte, Barranquilla

April 2021 — June 2021

Extended Essay, IB Professional Development

September 2021 — September 2021

Gamification: Motivation Psychology & the Art of Engagement,

Udemy

July 2020 — July 2020

Child Psychology: Advanced Level, Udemy

July 2020 — July 2020